♪ You think you're
so half polite ♪
♪ But I'm not
with you in mind ♪
♪ I am not with you tonight
♪ I've tried and tried
♪ You think you're
so half polite ♪
♪ But I'm not
with you in mind ♪
♪ I am not with you tonight
♪ I've tried and tried ♪
♪ But you think you're
so half polite ♪
♪ But I'm not
with you in mind ♪
♪ I am not with you tonight ♪
♪ I've tried and tried
♪ You think you're
so half polite ♪
♪ But I'm not
with you in mind ♪
♪ I am not with you ♪
Georgie!
Catherine.
♪ I've tried and tried ♪
♪ You think you're
so half polite ♪
♪ But I'm not with
you in my mine ♪
♪ I am not with you tonight ♪
♪ I've tried and tried ♪
♪ You think you're
so half polite ♪
♪ But I'm not
with you in mind ♪
♪ I'm not with you tonight
She's back.
Heya.
Georgie was asking for you.
I told him you hated him and
that you despised his baking.
You bitch.
You wouldn't like my family.
I'm excited for this weekend.
We could have just
done something here.
Well, I wanted to.
I want this weekend
to be special.
It's a big deal.
I guess.
It's just too much.
Well, I keep saying I
can help pay for things.
Where'd you get that?
I rented it.
It's a weekend, not a month.
Oh, wow.
Let's pull over.
We're already an hour behind
Oh, come on.
It'll be quick.
I love this kind of stuff.
Let's go upstairs.
Come on!
Step back from there.
It's dangerous.
It's fine.
Diane.
Stand there.
We booked the corner
top room suite, though.
I'm confused.
My apologies.
We've had a bit of a reshuffle
with a special guest who
just showed up last minute.
- A special guest?
- Yes.
How do I say it?
A marketing deal.
Our dates got moved
around, and my apologies.
I spent extra on that
room specifically.
We've been planning
this trip for months.
Again, we are very sorry.
All good?
Not really.
It's tiny.
It's fine.
I am just excited to spend
some time off with you.
Slightly boring
at this point.
Do you get what-- no.
No, I told him that we needed
the flight on Thursday,
not Friday.
He is utterly incompetent,
and this place
is nothing like they said.
I don't know what they're
expecting me to do with it.
It's in the middle of nowhere.
No, I know.
But, oh, the room is not
what they sold me on.
It is so small.
I'll be fine.
I'll figure it out.
It's just a couple of days.
Yeah.
I'll speak to you soon.
The pool is kind
of small, isn't it?
It looked bigger
in the pictures.
I don't know what
I'm gonna do with it.
Charlotte, by the way.
Hmm?
I wasn't originally
gonna come,
but then they ended up comping
the whole thing last minute.
And I have, like,
a deal with the chain,
so I'm sort of forced to come.
The pool looks
bigger in their photos.
Why not just make it look
bigger in your photos?
What's your name?
Catherine.
Well, lovely to meet you.
She feels bad.
I highly doubt that.
You should have seen
how she was talking
to her assistant or whoever.
She even offered
to swap rooms.
Try taking her up on it.
Look, she wants
to buy us dinner.
If you don't want to go,
it's fine, but I'm going.
Honestly, I was bouncing
back and forth between LA
and New York doing
makeup sponsorships.
Basically, selling
products to little girls.
And then I got
pulled back to Europe
for these travel campaigns, and
now I'm ready for something
new again.
You don't get lonely
traveling all alone?
No.
I am constantly meeting people.
And plenty of creators are
solo travelers, so you get
to know people along the way.
I don't know
if I could do it.
I feel like I'd feel unsafe
traveling by myself like that.
Yeah, it seems risky.
Nobody really knows
where you are.
Well, what's life
without a little risk?
You've traveled solo before.
Not really.
Only Europe.
When the two of us met, she
seemed so down on herself,
didn't seem to know anyone.
And then she just came
and swept me off of my feet.
You two are together?
Oh my god!
I thought you
were sisters or something.
Sisters.
Oh, this is so cute.
I mean, this is
actually our anniversary.
A whole year.
Oh my god.
And I'm here, just, like,
ruining the whole thing.
No, that's okay.
So what have you got planned?
Yeah, we're thinking of going
out to the countrysides,
maybe see a vineyard.
Oh, I actually have
this exclusive wine
tour happening tomorrow.
Sponsor thing.
I could get you guys an invite.
We have our own plans.
So how long have
you been in France?
Me?
Yeah.
You're American, no?
Yeah, but I've been in Europe
for a number of years.
America is so new.
There's something about modern
cities that just speaks to me.
Greener grass, I guess.
Totally.
So much more lush.
I just got back from
Japan, and I got
the most beautiful pictures.
Oh, Catherine's always
wanted to go see Asia.
We think we might
try to go next year.
You've never been?
No.
Bucket list, I guess.
I mean, you're always
talking about it.
Well, everyone's
gotta start somewhere.
I'm actually thinking about
going back to Bali once Europe
inevitably bores me.
I've got some
friends in Thailand,
and I'm definitely
so jealous.
She's nice.
Sure.
She means well.
I don't mind her.
She apparently helps
run this charity.
It's just the entitlement.
Girls like that
just take and take.
But if you take
their phones away,
they'd be completely
useless, dead in a week.
Are you jealous?
What?
No.
I just think girls like that
are single-handedly ruining
the next generation of women.
Someone should
teach them a lesson.
A little isolation
without their phones
would probably do them good.
Always so dramatic.
When I was a kid, I
spent a lot of time alone.
Did me good.
What?
Like, strand them all
alone with no phone
service and see how
long they survive?
See, now you're talking
like a psychopath.
It would make
a good reality show.
I bet no one would
notice if she disappeared.
What are you looking at?
Nothing.
Tomorrow, let's go
to the countryside.
Just you and me.
What we came here for.
Mm.
I'd like that.
You're up early.
Look at you, all done up.
Ah, yeah, you.
Long black with milk
and a little bowl of fruit.
Diane's still asleep?
Mm-hmm.
Oh, I've always
been an early riser,
though it's hard here
with how impossible
it is to get a proper latte.
There is nothing I hate
more than wasting the day
away before it's even begun.
Did she tell you the plan?
No.
Yeah, I was texting
her last night.
I sent her the tickets
for that beautiful vineyard,
very exclusive.
She mentioned she'd be happy to
take some photos for me today.
She is so talented.
She did?
Is that right?
Yeah, I was telling her
that she'd do so well being
a photographer for creators.
Yeah, I know some friends
that would love to have her.
I'm gonna set her up with them.
It's such a great
opportunity for her.
She's actually not feeling
very well this morning.
Oh, no.
Yeah, a stomach bug.
I think she's gonna stay
in for the rest of the day.
That's too bad.
But I'd be happy to be
your photographer for the day.
I actually know just
the place we should go.
Let me get her camera.
I'm definitely a red
wine connoisseur myself.
It's all Shiraz in this
area, Syrah grapes.
I'm more of a pinot noir girl.
Do you know much about wine?
No, not really.
Oh, you should learn.
There's so much more depth
to be explored once you
get beneath the typical wine.
I'd be happy to teach you.
Diane mentioned that you're
at school for computer science.
I was.
I dropped out.
I get it.
Pressure was too much.
No, it's not that.
I remember when I wasn't
sure what to do with my life.
We all find our way, though.
I am more than sure
you'll figure it out.
I think it's just around
the corner over here.
Ah, there it is.
Incredible.
Just wait till
you see inside.
I forgot how this works.
Diane was showing me.
Here, let me take
some with your phone.
Perfect.
A little to the left.
Oh, shit.
What's your password?
We don't-- [sighs] whatever.
It's 8546.
Let's go upstairs.
It's really cool up there.
Okay.
Ah, the lighting's
just perfect.
Here.
Stand over there.
The photos are
gonna be amazing.
It seems a bit unstable.
No, it's fine.
Diane and I were
here yesterday.
Okay.
It looks like a long drop.
Help me.
Help.
Please.
Please!
Help!
Hey.
Where have you been?
I texted you.
I went for a run
this morning.
I couldn't sleep.
Okay?
Well, I just went to the pool.
I wanna go get a shower.
Have you eaten?
Yeah.
I ate before I left.
I'll come join you in a bit.
Okay.
Before I forget, Charlotte,
she won't stop texting me.
She wants us to go
to that vineyard thing.
I told her that
we were busy, and
I was thinking that
the two of us could just--
Yeah, we should go.
The vineyard sounds nice.
Hi.
Yeah, but the original
vineyard was just
seven hectares in the 1965.
It's strange.
I texted her, but I still
haven't heard anything.
Maybe she got sick.
But you'd think
she'd let us know.
She lets us know
everything else about her.
And here, we have
the grapevine rose.
Now, can anyone guess--
which grape variety we
grow the most of here?
Syrah.
That is correct.
Very good.
This is better.
So nice of her
to give us the room.
I mean, she's gone, so--
Yeah.
It's strange of her
to run off like that.
I wonder if something happened.
I told you, girls like that
only care about themselves.
This weekend's shaping
up exactly as I'd hoped.
I could use a bit help.
Who's that?
Oh.
Just an old friend.
She's quite pretty.
Yeah.
I'm going to bed.
Night.
Do you need anything?
No, I'm good.
See you in a bit.
Diane?
I don't understand.
Is your name even Catherine?
Why do you have access
to Charlotte's account?
I can explain.
You've done this before.
Diane.
What were you
doing in Thailand?
I've never been to Thailand.
Yes, you have.
What did you read?
Several girls were killed.
I'm gonna call the police.
No, don't.
Please, Diane.
Diane.
Diane, I love you.
You lied to me.
I was going to tell you.
Tell me what?
That you're an actual
fucking psychopath?
Here's what's gonna happen.
♪ Give it to me ♪
♪ Yeah, yeah ♪
♪ No shoes at the door ♪
♪ No keys in the couch ♪
♪ No life in the tomb ♪
♪ Don't feed that ♪
♪ New lease on the car
♪ New lease on the house ♪
♪ New lease on my life
♪ I need that ♪
♪ Two trees in the yard ♪
♪ New leaves on the trees ♪
♪ They live to 180 amount ♪
♪ No smoke in the room ♪
♪ No smoke in the lounge ♪
♪ Had a joint
on the porch to myself ♪
♪ No feedback ♪
♪ Yeah ♪
♪ Yeah
♪ Give it to me
♪ No shoes at the door
♪ No keys in the couch ♪
♪ No life in the room ♪
♪ Don't feed that ♪
♪ New lease on a car ♪
♪ New lease on a house
♪ New lease on my life ♪
♪ I need that
♪ Two trees in the yard
♪ New leaves on the trees
♪ They live to 180 amount
♪ No smoke in the room ♪
♪ No smoke in the lounge ♪
♪ Had a joint to myself
on the porch ♪
♪ No feedback ♪
♪ Yeah ♪
♪ No feedback
She took my identity,
and nobody believed me.
That's the claim
of our next guest, who,
just over a year
ago, was embroiled
in controversy over the death
of her boyfriend, Ryan Evans.
We're taking you all the way
over to Thailand with this one.
A true trouble in paradise.
Authorities found the remains
of two women, Becky Wilson and
Laura Gallagher, on a small,
uninhabited island
in the Gulf of Thailand.
She returned with two bodies
on a boat, both Ryan Evans and
Jessica Matthews, claiming to
authorities that she had left
the murderer on the island.
However, when they showed
up, the island was empty.
No murderer.
The supposed suspect,
a woman known only
by the name CW, who has
a prominent birthmark
on the right side of her face.
Yet, somehow, no
clear photos of her
exist, no record of any kind.
She disappeared like
a ghost in the wind.
Which leads us to our guest,
who initially became a suspect,
but was ultimately
cleared of all charges
due to the lack of evidence.
Four dead bodies,
two others missing.
And no culprit.
Very excited
for our guest today,
finally breaking her silence
after all the controversy.
We gave you the infamous
Madison White.
Thanks for coming on.
Welcome to the show.
Thanks for having me.
I really appreciated
everything you guys
said when this all came out.
So you are
completely offline now?
It was too much.
I couldn't go anywhere,
but I'm feeling better now.
I'm back in school, and--
The harassment?
People blamed me.
I mean, you saw what
Ryan's family put out.
Madison always seemed off.
Our relationship was
put under a microscope.
And initially, everything she
put out painted him as abusive,
but then they started
to pick me apart.
Your follower count exploded.
"She put out."
What do you mean by that?
What she wrote about
Ryan on my account.
None of that was true.
I had to move.
People were showing
up at my house.
They found my phone number.
It was awful.
From what I
understand, you claim she
took over your social media.
Yes.
I was on that island
for four weeks.
So you claim.
So I claim?
You were posting throughout
that entire period.
She was posting.
A girl nobody
can seem to find.
I mean, she just disappears?
I don't understand this.
She took over my whole goddamn
life, my account, my banking.
You did delete your account
right after coming home.
Yeah.
The boat was stolen.
The owner was
a local fisherman.
You can't register
a boat as a foreigner.
All the stuff on it
belonged to Ryan or Jessica.
Not one item was owned by CW.
What kind of name is that even?
Like the network.
Yeah.
The whole thing reeks like
a bad made-for-TV movie.
She just brought that
stuff to get rid of it.
She must have had her stuff
stored somewhere else.
There is security footage
of her at the resort I was at.
The hotel confirmed
there was another guest.
It proves nothing.
And the video footage
is barely visible.
The resort is halfway
across the country
from where the island was.
We traveled.
How do you explain Becky and
Laura or the other two girls,
Rhea and Samantha, who they--
Still missing.
More has come out
linking you to them.
Your fingerprints are
all over Becky and
Laura's bodies, nobody else's.
I found them dead,
and I buried them.
What about her other
bungalow where she'd
been living in the jungle?
Rented by Becky Wilson.
The owner hasn't
even met anyone else.
If this CW person,
if she really
does exist, why did she do it?
What did she have to gain?
She took over my entire life.
Yeah, but why?
I don't know.
How did she get
off the island?
You said yourself, it
was miles off the coast.
You were stuck
there, no way off.
If she was able to get off
so easily, why not you?
I don't know.
I mean, according to you,
she's pretty recognizable.
So how does somebody
like that just disappear?
Hey, we're just trying
to get to the truth here.
You guys defended me.
That's the whole reason
I came onto this podcast.
The more that's come out, the
more complicated it all looks.
I was cleared of all charges.
Does that make you innocent?
Don't forget to use
the promo code Madison White
for an additional--
If you want to protect
yourself from individuals
like this, use Strong Ape VPN.
Ooh, ooh, ah, ah.
Protect your IP address
for only $9.99 a month.
It's a really great service.
Don't forget to use promo--
Thanks for coming in.
Thanks.
Hello?
You fucking lying cunt.
I have your address.
I'm gonna find you, and I'm--
Not again.
Hello?
Pizza delivery.
I didn't order any pizza.
Madison White?
I got, like, six pizzas
down here for you.
I didn't order any pizzas.
Come on, lady, just come
downstairs and talk to me.
Leave me the fuck alone!
Where were you last?
Good evening,
ladies and gentlemen.
This is the flight deck.
This is your captain speaking.
We are about to start
our final descent into Paris.
We should have
you on the ground
in approximately 30
minutes from now.
We can thank you
for joining us.
We wish you all a very
pleasant evening in Paris
or wherever
your travels might be.
This is for you.
Thank you.
Hey, guys.
I'm at Chateau Saint Laurent.
It is absolutely gorgeous here.
I'm having
a beautiful pool day.
You guys all have to come.
I'm gonna put up a little
code for you in my bio.
Who are you?
Hello.
I'm checking in.
Passport?
Madison White.
I was also wondering.
I had a couple friends
stay here a few weeks ago.
I'm trying to get
a hold of one of them.
Oh, we don't give
out information
about previous guests.
One girl who has
a birthmark and
another girl with
blonde hair, they were
here back around August 12.
What do you want
to know about them?
Oh, um--
What are their names?
Um.
You don't know their names.
Chateau Saint Laurent.
It is absolutely gorgeous here.
I'm having
a beautiful pool day.
You guys all have to come.
I'm gonna put up a little code
for you in my bio Hey, guys.
I'm at Chateau Saint Laurent.
It is absolutely gorgeous here.
I'm having
a beautiful pool day.
You guys--
Found you.
Bonjour?
Hello?
I'm trying to get
a hold of your daughter.
I don't know.
I don't speak French.
Diane.
I'm looking for Diane.
I'm trying to get
a hold of her.
Catherine?
Bali?
Indonesia?
No.
Merci.
Goodbye.
♪ Drop when the choppa
sing, gotta pop the bean ♪
♪ Pop the beam,
bust like pottery ♪
♪ Now they looking
lean, trim the fat ♪
♪ My autonomy,
taken by a fiend ♪
♪ No control of my properties,
of my faculties ♪
♪ Caught them in the backroom
like a nextbot ♪
♪ With the red dot,
running like a Spartan, make ♪
♪ them topple
with a head drop ♪
♪ Didn't want to be the one
to take you with the deadshot ♪
♪ I just want to be the one ♪
She's draining your dick,
but she's draining your wallet.
Like, dude, you need to put
your girl on a leash.
Yeah, whatever.
You know nothing about me and
my girl, you fucking dickhead.
My girl's not like that.
Women do not care about
the effort that you put in.
They just want to see
the winner, right?
As soon as the well
runs dry, she's out.
She's gone.
You'll be alone in a second.
See, women don't understand
the value of work.
They never had to.
That's why they just,
mm, mm, mm, look to us,
because they are opportunistic,
soulless creatures, really.
Everyone's looking
out for themselves.
You're just
hyperfocused on women.
I mean, men are just as bad--
- No, no, no no.
or worse.
A relationship with
a man is not opportunistic.
It is mutual.
You actually like each other.
I already told you,
my girl's not like that.
No.
See, you are a reflection
of how you see yourself,
and your reflection is that of
a pathetic little simp bitch.
This isn't fucking
rocket science, bro.
Lift some fucking weights.
Business only.
Do not let the women set
the press in the relationship.
Don't let a woman
dictate the relationship.
You know this, right?
Man.
Shit, I'm out.
I'm out.
Shit.
I'm getting tilted, bro.
Namaste, faggots.
That went well, I think.
Eh?
Did you see his reaction?
Hmm?
Did you watch?
A bit.
I mean, I thought
it went all right.
I just really
think you can push
further, get under
their skin more,
force them to be the dick.
You're the voice of reason.
Remember that.
- Yeah.
Yeah, yeah, yeah,
yeah, you're right.
You need some kind of spark,
something controversial.
Everything is so blasé.
People are getting bored.
You're dropping off.
♪ Separate the addict
from the pusher ♪
She's a fucking bitch, dude.
I gotta be honest with you.
You know, I used to have this
thing about not telling my guy
friends they should dump
their girls because, honestly,
if you want to mess your life
up, that's none of my business.
But clearly, you
need a wake up call.
You don't even
fucking know her.
I know that you're not happy.
That, I fucking know.
The way she treats you, dude.
The way that anytime anything
even goes remotely wrong,
she flies off
the fucking rails.
You don't know
the kind of work
that she's putting
in, though, bro.
Like, the stream
is popping off.
You don't believe half
the shit that you're saying.
And where the fuck
are those shots?
I'm giving these
kids purpose, man.
And we do need
a shake-up, you know,
make masculinity cool again.
My guy.
I give up.
We've completely lost
the male role model.
And, like, it's just
these young kids that
are, like, so fucking lost.
Okay, prove it.
She seems fuckable.
What are you talking about?
Ever since you've
gotten with Ariana,
you've been on this holier
than art thou bullshit.
Such a fucking pussy.
If you're such a man
like you say you are,
she shouldn't care if you
go over there and fuck her.
Hey, you know what?
Fine.
You want me to go
fucking talk to her?
I'll go fucking talk to her.
Okay, go.
I'll fucking do it, bro.
I'll go talk to her.
Go.
Fuck.
Hi.
♪ - Addictions ♪
♪ As long as there
are people-- ♪
Hey.
♪--there will be
addiction to drugs-- ♪
- I'm good.
- I'm not hitting on you.
Cool.
♪--sports,
and even to arts ♪
Hey.
Hey, hey.
Can I get another one
of these, and she'll have a--
The bill.
Thanks.
♪ And he who knows
how to pace himself, ♪
♪ can win any race ♪
I have a girlfriend.
I'm not hitting on you.
You just seem like the
loneliest girl in the world.
I hate places like this.
Okay, then why are you here?
I'm looking for someone.
Maybe you've seen her.
What, are you stalking her?
I'm-- I'm just joking.
Why are we looking
for this mystery girl, huh?
Did she do something to you?
She stole something from you.
She must have.
She killed a bunch of people.
Left me on an island to die.
Almost did, but managed
to strand her on it.
Okay.
Well, then how did she get off?
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
You seem familiar.
You remind me of someone.
Not a good thing.
Hey, hold on.
Wait, wait, wait,
wait, wait, just--
if I do run into this mystery
girl, how will I let you know?
What else do I need
to know about her?
Yeah!
Yo, motherfuckers.
Yo.
Morning, chat.
Good morning to all.
What's up, Benny?
I see you.
Yeah, it's late as fuck
here, but we're on the grind.
Grinding every
fucking day out here.
We all up late out here.
Benny, thanks for the five.
I got some videos.
This is some dog shit.
Oh, yeah.
Okay, this side.
We should take some more
photos by the pool later.
Oh, yeah.
I have some photos to show you.
It's gonna be beautiful.
Good.
Hold your hair.
Marissa finally got engaged.
Mm.
Ever since they've had that
kid, they've been dominating.
It's not even that cute.
She asked us
to come over later.
I said we would, but I
don't want to stay too late.
I noticed Nutrigrains hasn't
sent their last payment yet.
Have you followed up
with them about that?
Jacob.
What's up?
Are you listening?
Ah.
Yeah, no.
Okay, you need to be
on that because I
can't be the one who's--
- I know.
Right.
I know.
Hey.
I love you, okay?
You know that.
It's because I care.
One second.
You're not a murderer, are you?
What?
No?
Are you sure?
Unless there's
another girl in Bali
that looks exactly like you.
There's a girl looking for you.
Who?
Mentioned something about
a dead girl in France,
met you in Thailand.
It sounded ridiculous.
You'd get caught immediately.
How'd you get off the island?
Excuse me?
You're really not gonna
give me anything, huh?
Okay.
Just kidding.
Good luck, killer.
She's back.
Hey.
How's your day going?
Fine.
Several updates.
Few new messages
from the States.
Nothing too out of the ordinary
but flag worthy.
Let's pause all
communication on everything.
We may need to pack up and move
again, potentially quickly.
Is there any updates
on the investigation?
I haven't found
any new articles.
No, I think
we're in the clear.
Madison's here.
Why?
I don't know.
I think she's looking for me.
How does she
know you're here?
I don't know.
The only people who know
we're here are your parents.
Madison doesn't know
my parents, does she?
No.
Then how did she find us?
How did she find us?
All her accounts
are still inactive.
She's offline.
Not surprising.
Does she know your real name?
What else does she know?
She knows about Charlotte.
How?
Do something for me.
Let's do a search
for males ages 25 to 35,
brown eyes, short hair.
Anyone who's been here
in the last few weeks.
Got it.
Wait.
Hold.
Go back.
There.
Let's go!
Woo!
Yeah!
It's her.
What are you going to do?
She wouldn't be stupid
enough to come alone.
But it didn't seem like
she was with anyone.
What am I missing?
What if you just lay low?
She wouldn't be
able to find you.
Check this out.
You hear about those
murders in Thailand?
No?
Okay, okay.
Get this, get this.
So I'm at the club.
I'm chatting up
this chick, right?
Turns out her name
is Madison White.
Look, look.
She was arrested
in Thailand last year.
Last fucking year.
And she claims
she's here looking
for the real fucking killer,
this girl with the birthmark.
No way.
Yeah, yeah.
So the next day,
the next fucking day,
I run into that chick.
Yeah.
That fucking chick, bro.
Like, I only talked
to her for a second.
She wasn't giving me
shit, but it was her.
It was fucking her.
Do you think she did it?
I mean, I don't know, bro.
I don't fucking know.
Like, everything online
points to the first chick,
but I'm telling you,
chat, like, really?
Like, really?
This bitch is tiny, like--
Ah.
Is she hot?
I think we should leave.
No.
There's a better
way out of this.
Neither of them
can prove anything.
I just need--
She's a fucking redhead, bro.
you.
Like, that shit
might be nasty, right?
Like, when I went
up to her, like,
she was giving me the-- she was
giving me those fucking vibes.
I got some food for thought.
Some morning thoughts.
I always get these
comments asking me,
how can I acquire wealth?
What does it take
to become rich?
It's all mental.
It's all a mental game.
Let's just say that a man
wins the lottery, right?
Well, if he hasn't carved
out that mentality,
if he hasn't locked it
in, he's going to lose
it all in six weeks, right?
So don't be a wage cuck.
Find me a street
view to match this.
Got it.
Found it.
You can't love others
until you love yourself.
We've all heard this
a million times.
This is a lie.
We are living in a world of
corrupt morals and degeneracy.
Gender ideology cult is
coming for your children.
♪ Ay, ay ♪
♪ All this money
we made, made ♪
♪ Now they coming my way, way ♪
I'm telling you, man.
This girl is fucking hot, man.
She's just eating
out of my hand.
Look at this shit.
- You don't recognize her?
- What?
This girl?
I doubt she's gonna show.
No, my dude.
She said she's bring
your friends, man.
I'm telling you, bro.
You've got to get back
on the horse with me.
I've told you.
Man, you and me, single, it'd
feel like Ibiza all over again.
Come on.
I want my wingman back.
Oh my god.
Hi.
You're the one that came up
to me about that psychopath
that's been stalking me.
What?
So you're sure she meant you?
She called me and said
I did these awful things.
I don't understand.
I met her one time, and now
she's trying to frame me.
Maybe you can help me.
Hey, I'm scared.
I mean, just call the cops.
They're not gonna help me.
I can't prove it.
They'd just turn me away.
Please.
There you are.
I've been looking all
over the place for you.
Come on.
We're heading back to mine.
We're going.
Let's go.
All right.
Well, I gotta go, but we can--
I'll talk to you later.
What are you talking about?
No, no, no.
You're invited.
Come with us.
- Come with.
- Jesus Christ.
It's like this guy
cockblocks himself.
♪ I'm a Tusken, rob you,
I'll raid your whole casa ♪
♪ I'm barking like
a pitbull, I'm embarking ♪
♪ And armed with sigils
on my garments, disarm ya ♪
♪ They harmless, I know
they be running this bluff ♪
♪ We got murderers, robbers,
dropping from the copper ♪
♪ Got the armored plate, got
my knife and my revolver ♪
♪ Awe-struck, when they see
your head up at the potluck ♪
♪ Glocked up, taking
my shot to the top ♪
♪ I'm sick like a sneeze,
like a cough, like a wheeze ♪
♪ Take your throne,
I'ma seize it, ♪
♪ never needed any keys ♪
♪ You believe what you want,
but you leave looking gaunt ♪
♪ They don't
understand so I'ma put ♪
♪ it in the biggest font ♪
♪ Hop off my dick,
you a bitch ♪
♪ you can sit with
the rest of these ♪
♪ Honorless trick,
in the blink of an eye, ♪
♪ gon' get put to sleep ♪
♪ Stopping me not gon' be
how you topple my monopoly ♪
♪ But I'm only 26,
had to stop work ♪
♪ I'm always
in the background ♪
I just don't understand what
you think I can do about it.
I'm all alone here.
She's following me.
I'm scared.
Mm-hmm.
What?
She doesn't seem the type.
You don't
understand this girl.
She's like a chameleon.
One moment, she
pretends like she's
this small, innocent girl
who doesn't know anything,
and then she's
suddenly different.
She has this way
of making you come to her.
She finds out exactly what you
want and plays right into it.
I wouldn't be surprised
if she was twisting her way
into your life as we speak.
What?
She's crazy.
She probably gets
a kick out of it.
Maybe it's just fun
for her or she's jealous.
I don't know.
Maybe she's just nuts.
I'm scared.
You just-- you
have this energy.
I feel safe with you.
Oh my god!
What are you doing?
Dude.
Can we go somewhere
more private?
Whoa, listen.
Just-- I have a girlfriend.
I don't care.
I do.
I thought you were some
strong male role model.
I've never cheated
on my girlfriend.
I love her.
Hey, I can help you.
I need you to help me
confront her publicly.
She needs to be exposed.
Do you still have her number?
I do.
I think she
knows where I live.
Can I stay at yours?
No.
I can't be alone right now.
We can go to my place
tomorrow and figure it out, but
not tonight.
You can stay here, but--
I get it.
So honorable of you.
Oh, yeah.
Oh, fuck me right there.
Uh-huh.
You like that,
you little bitch?
You're pathetic.
What the fuck?
Who the fuck are you?
I-- I know Jacob.
Okay?
He's not here.
I'm waiting for him.
And you just decided
to go on his computer?
Yeah.
He said I could.
Who are you?
You're in my house.
I'm calling Jacob.
Yeah, I'm gonna go.
No, you're not, actually.
I'm gonna call the police.
You can talk to them.
What do you want to know?
If I fucked him?
I don't know what your little
setup is here, but yeah, I did.
She's back.
Hey.
Hi.
Hello.
I'm gonna take them off.
I don't want to be lied to.
I've been hurt before.
I want to be
able to be honest.
Tell me something then.
Like what?
Like-- like what
happened to your eye?
I got stranded on an island
in the middle of the ocean.
Someone got the best
of me and left me to die.
What?
Yeah.
True story.
How'd you get off?
What?
Of the island.
How'd you get off of it?
That's what
you're attaching to?
I've done a lot of things
I'm not exactly proud of.
We've all done things
we're not happy with.
It's what we do with
it that matters.
Diane?
No, no, no, no.
No, no, no no, no,
no, no, no, no.
Wake up.
Wake up No, no, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Wake up.
No, I didn't mean to.
No, no, no, no, no.
I'd like to be able
to be honest with you.
I'll be right back.
All good?
Yeah.
I love you.
Come on, Jacob.
- Ariana?
- Cameron.
Thank god.
Where's Jacob?
He's-- Jacob?
Cameron.
Jacob is--
Cameron, where
the fuck is he?
Fuck.
Yo, bitch, calm down.
Cameron, I swear to god, you
put him on the fucking phone
right now.
How about you pack
your little bags and move on?
Because Jacob is in my room,
and he's not alone.
And he told me everything.
He did?
Yeah.
He did.
He's over you, and he's
sick of all your bullshit.
And I don't think
he cares what you
do, so why don't you fuck off?
No.
What?
Wake up, big boy.
Come on.
Wake up.
It's time to go.
Oh.
Fuck me.
Can I use your phone?
I think I broke mine.
Do you want my help or not?
Just--
We should go.
You like that,
you little bitch?
You're pathetic.
Hey, dude.
Can I talk to you for a second?
Yeah.
I'll meet you out there.
What the fuck?
Are you jerking off?
I-- uh--
Oh, look, look.
Listen.
About that chick,
there's nothing going on.
Hey, do you remember
that blonde that you
matched with on Tinder?
Never mind.
It's way too complicated.
That girl, she might
be wanted for murder.
What?
Dude, I have this whole plan.
She thinks I'm falling
for it, but I'm
gonna catch her red-handed.
I mean, Ariana
doesn't know about it.
But man, I'm
telling you, this is
gonna bring the stream
to the next fucking level,
like, viral shit, bro.
Right.
Yeah.
What's up, man?
You good?
So you haven't
talked to Ariana yet?
No.
No, man.
It's a surprise.
She's been trying to find ways
to build up the brand, bro,
but this is it.
This is fucking it.
Hey, my phone's busted,
but I'm going home.
If she calls, tell her I'm
bringing home a gold mine.
It's just weird
because Ariana doesn't normally
do this kind of stuff.
Jacob.
How did you get in here?
The door was open.
She's not moving, Jacob.
What the fuck did you do?
Hey.
No.
No, no, no.
What the fuck?
Oh, shit.
It's time to turn
yourself in.
It's over.
Why in the hell do
you think I'd do that?
You're gonna run out
of places to run away to.
You think--
I had nothing to do with her.
- What did you do?
- Me?
I didn't.
She-- when your phone texted
me, I knew it was her.
I came early like
we talked about.
I did what you said.
She pretended to be
you to Cameron,
and exactly like you
said, she came up to us.
You two were setting me up?
She's manipulating you.
It's her.
The door was wide
open when we got here.
- Oh, fuck.
- Jacob, I told you.
She's doing exactly
what I said.
Which one of you did this?
Which one of you did this!
Jacob, I swear.
She's been playing
you this whole time.
I told you she'd tried to
entwine herself into your life.
Fuck you.
I've been with Jacob
this entire time.
How would I--
What the fuck?
Sorry.
I'm sorry.
You ran.
You murdering bitch.
What the fuck?
Ah.
She's back.
Hello?
How's your day going?
You all right?
What is this?
I know you.
You're Diane.
Obviously.
She killed you, too.
Who are you talking about?
She did, didn't she?
I don't know what
you're talking about.
What's wrong, honey?
Just left you
like everyone else.
Who are you talking about?
Catherine.
Why did she do it?
I just want us to be happy.
It's okay what you do.
I understand now.
I want to help.
Oh.
Oh, god.
Hey.
Oh, fuck.
You're gonna be okay.
If I could-- ah.
Hey, hey.
You're gonna be okay.
She's-- she's gone.
She's gone.
You're safe.
I just need to get
this-- oh, fuck.
Let me get this off.
There we go.
You're safe.
I just gotta get you up here.
Come on.
There you go.
There we go.
Oh my god.
Oh, my god.
You weren't kidding.
She's nuts.
Oh, my god.
Wake up.
There you are.
Yeah.
There you go.
We're gonna be okay.
Hey, you're gonna to be okay.
Let me just-- no,
no, no, no, no.
Stay.
You're gonna be okay.
I just need-- Hey, I need your
phone so I can call someone.
Fuck.
I need to call someone Fuck.
Oh.
Oh my-- oh, fuck.
Okay, I think she
missed my organs.
You're right.
She's a murderer.
The cops will
know what to do.
Yeah.
Hey.
You were right, too.
She told me all these
things about you.
She tried to get into my life.
They'll arrest her.
It needs to be public.
It just doesn't make sense
why you pretended to-- oh.
Oh, my stomach.
Wait.
Why were you
in my house last night?
You like that,
you little bitch?
You're pathetic.
You broke in?
I don't-- I don't understand.
That's too bad.
She killed you
and your girlfriend all
because you poisoned the world.
Her words, not mine.
I'm starting to agree.
You're a cancer.
And sometimes there
needs to be someone
who cuts the cancer out.
Madison!
You can come out now.
We all up late out here.
Fake and gay.
Wait.
What the actual fuck?
Who's the dead girl?
This is fucked up.
Did she actually
just murder Jacob?
Holy shit.
Step on me, Mommy.
Jacob deserved it.
I'm in love.
Girl, you fine as hell.
Jacob is a good boy.
Fact.
She's a goddess.
Incredible.
This is why.
Jacob can burn in hell.
Hot.
I see you.
I would risk it.
He let me down.
Frown.
Goodbye, Diane.
Goodbye, Madison.
Does she have an OnlyFans?
I bet she's a killer
in the sheets, too.
What's your name?
I'm in love.
At first, I was upset, but
then I remembered that there's
no such thing as bad press.
And it's actually genius
if you think about it
because I've never heard
of a single public figure who
had a sex tape that
hurt their career.
In fact, sex tapes
help careers.
They elevate careers,
and all he has to do
is do a little
bit of a rebrand.
And if he pitches
that correctly,
then this is
a fantastic opportunity.
What the fuck?
What are you doing here?
♪ You think you're
so half polite ♪
♪ But I'm not
with you in mind ♪
♪ I am not with you tonight ♪
♪ I've tried and tried
♪ You think you're
so half polite ♪
♪ But I'm not
with you in mind ♪
♪ I am not with you tonight ♪
♪ I've tried and tried ♪
♪ But you think you're
so half polite ♪
♪ But I'm not
with you in mind ♪
♪ I am not with you tonight ♪
♪ I've tried and tried ♪
♪ But you think you're
so half polite ♪
♪ But I'm not
with you in mind ♪
♪ I am not with you tonight ♪
♪ I've tried and tried ♪
♪ But you think
you're so divine ♪
Why are you running away?